<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Major Project</string>
    <string name="mobility_companies_heading">Mobility Companies</string>
    <string name="crm_companies_heading">CRM Companies</string>
    <string name="cloud_companies_heading">Cloud services Companies</string>
    <string name="collaboration_companies_heading">Collaboration Tools Companies</string>
    <string name="communication_companies_heading">Communication Companies</string>
    <string name="advertisement_companies_heading">Advertisement Companies</string>
    <string name="payment_companies_heading">Payment Companies</string>
    <string name="trading_companies_heading">Trading Companies</string>
    <string name="investment_companies_heading">Investment Banks</string>
    <string name="gaming_companies_heading">Gaming Companies</string>
    <string name="entertainment_companies_heading">Entertainment Companies</string>
    <string name="about_mobility_companies">
        <b>=></b> Mobility is the industry of transporting people and goods.\n
        <b>=></b> Revenue in the Ride-hailing and Taxi segment is projected to reach US$12.77bn in 2023.\n
        <b>=></b> Revenue is expected to show an annual growth rate (2023-2027) of 0.12%, resulting in a projected market volume of US$12.83bn by 2027.
    </string>
    <string name="about_Ecommerce_companies">
        <b>=></b> E-commerce or Electronic commerce is the trading of goods and services on the Internet.\n
        <b>=></b> The global ecommerce growth rate for 2023 is forecast at 10.4% ,bring global ecommerce sales worldwide to $6.3 trillion.\n
        <b>=></b> India is the 8th largest market for ecommerce with a predicted revenue of US$79,923.8 million by 2023.
    </string>
    <string name="about_crm_companies">
        <b>=></b> A CRM company essentially provides a central place where businesses can store customer and prospect data, track customer interactions, and share this information with colleagues.\n
        <b>=></b> They allow businesses to manage relationships with customers, helping the business to grow.\n
    </string>
    <string name="about_cloud_companies">
        <b>=></b> Cloud service provider companies use their own data centers and compute resources to host cloud computing-based infrastructure and platform services for customer organizations.\n
        <b>=></b> Cloud services are typically priced using various pay-as-you-go subscription models.
    </string>
    <string name="about_collaboration_companies">
        <b>=></b> Collaboration tools enable employees to work together on a project without being in the same location.\n
        <b>=></b> Online collaboration tools are apps, software programs, or platforms that help businesses and their people streamline the creative process, and work together more effectively, and efficiently.
    </string>
    <string name="about_communication_companies">
        <b>=></b> They provide programmable communication tools for making and receiving text messages, and performing other communication functions using its web services APIs.\n
        <b>=></b> They are a customer engagement platform used by hundreds of thousands of businesses and more than ten million developers worldwide to build unique, personalized experiences for their customers.
    </string>
    <string name="about_advertisement_companies">
        <b>=></b> Advertising companies focus on providing monetization products to digital publishers.\n
        <b>=></b> The services include search, display, native, video, and mobile advertising to monetize publishers inventory.
    </string>
    <string name="about_payment_companies">
        <b>=></b> A payment service provider is a third-party company that assists businesses to accept electronic payments, such as credit cards and debit cards payments.\n
        <b>=></b> PSPs act as intermediaries between those who make payments, i.e. consumers, and those who accept them, i.e. retailers.\n
        <b>=></b> The global payment as a service market size was valued at USD 13.88 billion in 2022 and is expected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 15.2% from 2023 to 2030.
    </string>
    <string name="about_trading_companies">
        <b>=></b> They are investment platforms that offers a new way of investing money with stockbroking and direct mutual funds.\n
        <b>=></b> They provide user interface to make investing easy, accessible, transparent, and paperless, enabling users to invest in mutual funds without any hassles.
    </string>
    <string name="about_investment_companies">
        <b>=></b> They are leading global investment banking, securities and investment management firm that provides a wide range of financial services to a substantial and diversified client base.\n
        <b>=></b> They are leaders in investment banking, financial services for consumers and small business, commercial banking, financial transactions processing and asset management.
    </string>
    <string name="about_gaming_companies">
        <b>=></b> They provide a fantasy gaming platform for multiple sports such as fantasy cricket, football, basketball, kabaddi, hockey, volleyball, handball and baseball.\n
        <b>=></b> It is an online game where users create a virtual team of real-life players and earn points based on the performances of these players in real matches.
    </string>
    <string name="about_entertainment_companies">
        <b>=></b> These are subscription-based streaming services that allows their members to watch TV shows and movies on an internet-connected device.\n
        <b>=></b> Total revenue in the Entertainment segment is projected to reach US$29.35bn in 2022. Total revenue is expected to show an annual growth rate (CAGR 2022-2027) of 6.65%, resulting in a projected market volume of US$42.54bn by 2027.
    </string>
</resources>