<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Major Project</string>
    <string name="mobility_companies_heading">Mobility Companies</string>
    <string name="crm_companies_heading">CRM Companies</string>
    <string name="cloud_companies_heading">Cloud services Companies</string>
    <string name="collaboration_companies_heading">Collaboration Tools Companies</string>
    <string name="communication_companies_heading">Communication Companies</string>
    <string name="about_mobility_companies">
        <b>=></b> Mobility is the industry of transporting people and goods.\n
        <b>=></b> Revenue in the Ride-hailing and Taxi segment is projected to reach US$12.77bn in 2023.\n
        <b>=></b> Revenue is expected to show an annual growth rate (2023-2027) of 0.12%, resulting in a projected market volume of US$12.83bn by 2027.
    </string>
    <string name="about_Ecommerce_companies">
        <b>=></b> E-commerce or Electronic commerce is the trading of goods and services on the Internet.\n
        <b>=></b> The global ecommerce growth rate for 2023 is forecast at 10.4% ,bring global ecommerce sales worldwide to $6.3 trillion.\n
        <b>=></b> India is the 8th largest market for ecommerce with a predicted revenue of US$79,923.8 million by 2023.
    </string>
    <string name="about_crm_companies">
        <b>=></b> A CRM company essentially provides a central place where businesses can store customer and prospect data, track customer interactions, and share this information with colleagues.\n
        <b>=></b> They allow businesses to manage relationships with customers, helping the business to grow.\n
    </string>
    <string name="about_cloud_companies">
        <b>=></b> Cloud service provider companies use their own data centers and compute resources to host cloud computing-based infrastructure and platform services for customer organizations.\n
        <b>=></b> Cloud services are typically priced using various pay-as-you-go subscription models.
    </string>
    <string name="about_collaboration_companies">
        <b>=></b> Collaboration tools enable employees to work together on a project without being in the same location.\n
        <b>=></b> Online collaboration tools are apps, software programs, or platforms that help businesses and their people streamline the creative process, and work together more effectively, and efficiently.
    </string>
    <string name="about_communication_companies">
        <b>=></b> They provide programmable communication tools for making and receiving text messages, and performing other communication functions using its web services APIs.\n
        <b>=></b> They are a customer engagement platform used by hundreds of thousands of businesses and more than ten million developers worldwide to build unique, personalized experiences for their customers.
    </string>
</resources>