<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Major Project</string>
    <string name="mobility_companies_heading">Mobility Companies</string>
    <string name="crm_companies_heading">CRM Companies</string>
    <string name="cloud_companies_heading">Cloud services Companies</string>
    <string name="collaboration_companies_heading">Collaboration Tools Companies</string>
    <string name="communication_companies_heading">Communication Companies</string>
    <string name="advertisement_companies_heading">Advertisement Companies</string>
    <string name="payment_companies_heading">Payment Companies</string>
    <string name="trading_companies_heading">Trading Companies</string>
    <string name="investment_companies_heading">Investment Banks</string>
    <string name="gaming_companies_heading">Gaming Companies</string>
    <string name="entertainment_companies_heading">Entertainment Companies</string>
    <string name="system_design_heading">System Design</string>
    <string name="programming_languages_heading">Programming Languages</string>
    <string name="dsa_heading">Data Structures and Algorithms</string>
    <string name="oops_heading">Object Oriented Programming</string>
    <string name="dbms_heading">Database Management System</string>
    <string name="os_heading">Operating System</string>
    <string name="se_heading">Software Engineering</string>
    <string name="cn_heading">Computer Networks</string>
    <string name="about_mobility_companies">
        <b>=></b> Mobility is the industry of transporting people and goods.\n
        <b>=></b> Revenue in the Ride-hailing and Taxi segment is projected to reach US$12.77bn in 2023.\n
        <b>=></b> Revenue is expected to show an annual growth rate (2023-2027) of 0.12%, resulting in a projected market volume of US$12.83bn by 2027.
    </string>
    <string name="about_Ecommerce_companies">
        <b>=></b> E-commerce or Electronic commerce is the trading of goods and services on the Internet.\n
        <b>=></b> The global ecommerce growth rate for 2023 is forecast at 10.4% ,bring global ecommerce sales worldwide to $6.3 trillion.\n
        <b>=></b> India is the 8th largest market for ecommerce with a predicted revenue of US$79,923.8 million by 2023.
    </string>
    <string name="about_crm_companies">
        <b>=></b> A CRM company essentially provides a central place where businesses can store customer and prospect data, track customer interactions, and share this information with colleagues.\n
        <b>=></b> They allow businesses to manage relationships with customers, helping the business to grow.\n
    </string>
    <string name="about_cloud_companies">
        <b>=></b> Cloud service provider companies use their own data centers and compute resources to host cloud computing-based infrastructure and platform services for customer organizations.\n
        <b>=></b> Cloud services are typically priced using various pay-as-you-go subscription models.
    </string>
    <string name="about_collaboration_companies">
        <b>=></b> Collaboration tools enable employees to work together on a project without being in the same location.\n
        <b>=></b> Online collaboration tools are apps, software programs, or platforms that help businesses and their people streamline the creative process, and work together more effectively, and efficiently.
    </string>
    <string name="about_communication_companies">
        <b>=></b> They provide programmable communication tools for making and receiving text messages, and performing other communication functions using its web services APIs.\n
        <b>=></b> They are a customer engagement platform used by hundreds of thousands of businesses and more than ten million developers worldwide to build unique, personalized experiences for their customers.
    </string>
    <string name="about_advertisement_companies">
        <b>=></b> Advertising companies focus on providing monetization products to digital publishers.\n
        <b>=></b> The services include search, display, native, video, and mobile advertising to monetize publishers inventory.
    </string>
    <string name="about_payment_companies">
        <b>=></b> A payment service provider is a third-party company that assists businesses to accept electronic payments, such as credit cards and debit cards payments.\n
        <b>=></b> PSPs act as intermediaries between those who make payments, i.e. consumers, and those who accept them, i.e. retailers.\n
        <b>=></b> The global payment as a service market size was valued at USD 13.88 billion in 2022 and is expected to expand at a compound annual growth rate (CAGR) of 15.2% from 2023 to 2030.
    </string>
    <string name="about_trading_companies">
        <b>=></b> They are investment platforms that offers a new way of investing money with stockbroking and direct mutual funds.\n
        <b>=></b> They provide user interface to make investing easy, accessible, transparent, and paperless, enabling users to invest in mutual funds without any hassles.
    </string>
    <string name="about_investment_companies">
        <b>=></b> They are leading global investment banking, securities and investment management firm that provides a wide range of financial services to a substantial and diversified client base.\n
        <b>=></b> They are leaders in investment banking, financial services for consumers and small business, commercial banking, financial transactions processing and asset management.
    </string>
    <string name="about_gaming_companies">
        <b>=></b> They provide a fantasy gaming platform for multiple sports such as fantasy cricket, football, basketball, kabaddi, hockey, volleyball, handball and baseball.\n
        <b>=></b> It is an online game where users create a virtual team of real-life players and earn points based on the performances of these players in real matches.
    </string>
    <string name="about_entertainment_companies">
        <b>=></b> These are subscription-based streaming services that allows their members to watch TV shows and movies on an internet-connected device.\n
        <b>=></b> Total revenue in the Entertainment segment is projected to reach US$29.35bn in 2022. Total revenue is expected to show an annual growth rate (CAGR 2022-2027) of 6.65%, resulting in a projected market volume of US$42.54bn by 2027.
    </string>
    <string name="about_system_design">
        <b>=></b> Systems design is the process of defining elements of a system like modules, architecture, components and their interfaces and data for a system based on the specified requirements.\n
        <b>=></b> The goal of system design is to allocate the requirements of a large system to hardware and software components.\n
        <b>=></b> System design interviews are an important step in the hiring process for many software engineering roles, particularly for positions that involve building and scaling complex systems.
    </string>
    <string name="about_programming_languages">
        <b>=></b> A programming language is a way for programmers (developers) to communicate with computers. Programming languages consist of a set of rules that allows string values to be converted into various ways of generating machine code, or, in the case of visual programming languages, graphical elements.\n
        <b>=></b> The languages that are used to write a program or set of instructions are called "Programming languages". Programming languages are broadly categorized into three types − Machine level language. Assembly level language. High-level language.\n
        <b>=></b>  These programming languages are written in lines of code. When its arranged in the right order, it can be used to create software programs.
    </string>
    <string name="about_dsa">
        <b>=></b> DSA stands for Data Structures and Algorithms. It is also sometimes referred to as PSDS - Problem Solving Data Structures. DSA is applied in problem-solving and enables developers to learn to write efficient code. The quality of the code can be judged by how much memory and time it consumes.\n
        <b>=></b> Data structure and Algorithm (DSA) is applied in all disciplines of software development. DSA is the building block of the software development process. It is not limited to a single programming language. Although programming languages evolve or get dormant over time, DSA is incorporated into all of these languages.\n
        <b>=></b> Product Based Companies place so much emphasis on Data Structures and Algorithms because it demonstrate the problem-solving ability of a candidate. There is no room to craft elaborate stories and this means that either the candidate can solve the problem or they cant.\n
        <b>=></b> DSA is a must to crack the tech interviews at top product based companies.
    </string>
    <string name="about_oops">
        <b>=></b> Object-Oriented Programming System (OOPs) is a programming concept that works on the principles of abstraction, encapsulation, inheritance, and polymorphism.\n
        <b>=></b> It allows users to create objects they want and create methods to handle those objects.\n
        <b>=></b> Features of OOPS makes it easy for programmers to solve complex scenarios.\n
        <b>=></b> OOPS is one of the most important part of the tech interviews.
    </string>
    <string name="about_dbms">
        <b>=></b> A database management system (or DBMS) is essentially nothing more than a computerized data-keeping system.\n
        <b>=></b> Users of the system are given facilities to perform several kinds of operations on such a system for either manipulation of the data in the database or the management of the database structure itself.\n
        <b>=></b> For example: MySQL, Oracle, etc are a very popular commercial database which is used in different applications.\n
        <b>=></b> DBMS is also very important part of the tech interviews.
    </string>
    <string name="about_os">
        <b>=></b> An operating system is system software that manages computer hardware and software resources, and provides common services for computer programs.\n
        <b>=></b> An operating system (OS) is the program that, after being initially loaded into the computer by a boot program, manages all of the other application programs in a computer. The application programs make use of the operating system by making requests for services through a defined application program interface (API).\n
        <b>=></b> OS is the most essential and vital part of any tech interviews.
    </string>
    <string name="about_se">
        <b>=></b> Software Engineering focuses on analysing the needs and requirements of users to design, deploy, and test new software.\n
        <b>=></b> This subject mainly revolves around the concepts of designs, requirements, design and implementation, software testing, software evolution, project planning, quality management....
    </string>
    <string name="about_cn">
        <b>=></b> A computer network is a set of computers sharing resources located on or provided by network nodes.\n
        <b>=></b> Computers use common communication protocols over digital interconnections to communicate with each other.\n
        <b>=></b> Computer networking refers to interconnected computing devices that can exchange data and share resources with each other. These networked devices use a system of rules, called communications protocols, to transmit information over physical or wireless technologies.\n
        <b>=></b> Computer Networks is also one of the most important part of the tech interviews.
    </string>
</resources>